字幕组
ZiMuZu.tv
原创翻译  双语字幕
最快首发美剧、日剧下载请登录
字幕组网站www.ZiMuZu.tv
翻译:  芝小士和番小茄   狼人之影赛太公
翻译:  Eunice    洗七里
校对:  红V指日可待赛太公
时间轴:  三水
后期:  瓜瓜    总监： 怀念浓子的瓜瓜
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    美剧炸了
了解最新影视资讯字幕信息
摩  登
家  庭
第八季 第十二集
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
手机APP搜索
人人影视字幕组
垃圾  垃圾
Crap. Crap.
辣鸡  腊鸡
Crappacino. Charlie Craplin.
在哥伦比亚  如果有老头开始朝着信件吼
In Colombia, when the old man starts yelling at the mail,
我们就把他放到沙洲上  等大浪送他归西
We put them on a sandbar and wait for the tide to come in.
迪尔加多遇到了情人节的两难选择
Well, Delgado's got a doozy of a Valentine's dilemma.
我发了短信试探两个妞
I texted out feelers for two dates.
维琪·卢是我的首选  但是亚历克莎·波茨
Vicky Noh is top choice, but Alexa Potts has been doing
最近走坏女孩风也让我挺心动
this bad-girl thing lately I'm into.
所以等待卢答应的同时
So, while I wait for a yes from Noh,
我要把波茨留在候补位置
I've got to keep Potts on the back burner.
要命了  他还在唧唧歪歪吗
Oh, my God. Is it still talking?
杰  你真没礼貌
Jay, that's so rude!
他总是想太多
He overthinks everything.
只要坏女孩有机会  你上就对了
If you have a shot at the bad girl, jump.
我也说不准
I don't know.
她有个继父
She has a stepdad who
只关注她性感的姐姐
only pays attention to her hot older sister.
我会亲自帮你拨电话给她
I will dial the phone for you.
乔的学校打电话来  说他惹麻烦了
That was Joe's school. He's in trouble.
我们得去跟老师见面
We need to go meet with the teacher.
他搞了什么事
What the hell did he do?
他打劫银行并挟持了18个人质
He robbed a bank and took 18 hostages.
我哪知道啊  快走吧
How would I know? Let's go.
没戏了
It's a no-go.
亚历克莎今晚想在大浴缸泡澡
Alexa wanted to use the hot tub tonight,
但她貌似找不到泳衣  没衣服穿
but apparently can't find her bathing suit.
如果你回家时身上没有淡啤酒味和池水氯味
If you don't come home smelling of light beer and chlorine,
你就不用回来了
Do not come home at all.
亲爱的
Uh, honey?
情人节快乐  我的爱
Happy Valentine's day, my love!
谢谢
Oh, thank you. Ooh.
我好喜欢这个  这是什么啊
I love this. What is it?
当年我们初吻时  就坐在这个门廊秋千上
It's the actual porch swing where we had our first kiss.
-不会吧  -你看看
- No. - Check it out.
25年前在后面刻的字还在呢
The carvings are still on the back from 25 years ago.
天啊  "菲尔爱克莱尔"
Oh, my gosh. "Phil hearts Claire."
亲爱的  这个放在我们家门廊上一定很赞
Oh, honey, this is gonna look so great out on our porch.
真不敢相信你把它弄回来了
I can't believe you did this.
没什么啦
It was nothing.
不过是打了几个电话  开了半天的车
I made a few calls, drove half a day...
喝了点酒  跟有咸猪手的同志房东讨价还价
..had campari and haggled with a handsy gay landlord,
接着拆解这秋千  装上货车
took the swing apart, loaded it in a van,
结果车在沙漠里没油了
ran out of gas in the desert,
还被一个可疑的州警骚扰
got harassed by a shady state trooper,
最后忍着剧烈的偏头痛开回家
and drove back with a blinding migraine.
反正是小菜一碟啦
But easy-peasy.
我超喜欢的
I love it.
敲敲门  情人节快乐
Knock, knock. Happy Valentine's day
或是我称之为"最适合去逛超市的一晚"
or, as I call it, "The best night to go to the grocery store."
这是你的情人节礼物
And here is your valentine's gift.
我亲手在办公室包装的
I wrapped it myself in the office,
然后像个傻子一样  把礼物忘在那了  所以...
And then, like a dingdong, I left it there, so...
闪闪惹人爱啊
Whoa, sparkly.
跟你一样  所以我才选这张包装纸
Just like you. That's why I picked the wrapping.
-绝对是她选的  -拆开看看吧
- She sure did. - Yeah. Go ahead.
克莱尔  我好像猜到这是什么了
Claire, I think I know what this is.
真不敢相信你送我这个
I can't believe you did this.
可不是嘛
I know, right?
你送我的是一块旧手表
You got me an old watch.
-很酷吧  -太酷了
- Pretty cool, right? - So cool.
我喜怒不形于色功力很高
I've got a crazy-good poker face,
但其实我并不喜欢那块手表
but I didn't love the watch.
我之前一直强烈暗示她
I'd been dropping these big hints
哈里·胡迪尼  著名魔术师  逃脱艺术家
我想要胡迪尼的真品手铐
about a pair of genuine Houdini handcuffs
我们当地魔术用品店里在打折
on sale at a local magic shop.
是他1923年著名的眼镜蛇棺材逃脱表演里用过的
They're from his famous coffin of cobras escape of 1923.
那套戏法实在太震撼了
The trick was so shocking
姑娘们看了都自然开始分娩
that women went into spontaneous labor
汉子们看了都开始疯狂对打
and the men paired off in violent fighting.
表好像不会动
I, uh, don't think it's working.
我觉得吧
Oh, well, I mean,
我虽然是第一次看到这块表
I'm just seeing this watch for the first time,
但它好像有自动上发条机制
But it looks like it's got a self-winder.
-你只要动动手臂...  -没错
You just move your... Yeah.
给表上发条了它才会动
...arm around to keep it going.
我该走了
I should probably get going.
我母亲在卡车里等我
Mother's waiting in the truck...
她的耐心很有限
...And she's patient until she isn't.
我也该去上班了
Oh, and I've got to get to work, too,
得赶在那些单身妹子前开工
before all the single gals show up.
要不然等她们在洗手间大哭  往墙上砸
It's pretty hard to concentrate with all the bathroom crying
吃了一半的巧克力时  就很难集中精神工作了
and the half-eaten chocolates getting hurled at the wall.
-工作顺利  -我会的
- Have a good one. - I will.
花很漂亮啊
Wow. Those are nice.
是啊  在前廊发现的
Yeah, they were on the front porch.
是一个神秘的仰慕者送的
They're from a mystery admirer.
卡片写着"你不知道自己的魔力"
The card says, "You don't know your power."
这是我的错
Oh, that's my bad.
我之前穿着拉拉队短裤
I was power-washing the flagstones
-使劲在洗石板路  -花是送给我的
- in my old cheer shorts -- - They're for me.
别问我是谁送的
Yeah, don't ask who they're from,
因为我也不知道  但我会找出那个人
because I don't know, but I will find out.
你手臂怎么了
What happened to your arm?
我在给这块旧表上发条
Oh, I am winding an old watch
是你妈妈送给我的情人节礼物
that your mother gave me for Valentine's day.
挺不对等啊  你可是送了她这么赞的秋千
Oh. That's pretty uneven. You gave her this awesome swing.
妈妈到底从哪里捡到你这个暖男
Man, where did mom find a guy as sweet as you?
其实是她开车撞到我
Actually, she hit me with her car
我当时正在肯德基的停车场跳霹雳舞
when I was break-dancing in a KFC parking lot.
再说你妈妈也不是不浪漫
And your mother's not unromantic.
她只是最近工作很忙
She's just been busy with work lately.
反正你们的确也结婚25年了
Well, you've been married for like 25 years.
这话什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
你们俩之间的浪漫火花
You guys are overdue for the romance
老早前就该熄灭了
to fizzle out a little bit.
不知名的跟踪狂给你送了
Oh, well, it's nice to know that some dime-store posies
一束便宜的花
from an unnamed stalker have
你就瞬间变成情感专家了吗  真不错
made you an expert on matters of the heart.
其实你妈妈还是有浪漫细胞的
It so happens that your mother is still very romantic,
等我今天下午去她办公室送惊喜
which I will prove with a surprise visit
就能证明给你看
to her office this afternoon.
我来猜猜看  你在屋里拼好秋千
Let me guess -- you built this inside
而你没事先量过门的高度
and didn't measure the door?
卡片说得对  你不知道自己的...
Card was right. You don't know your own power...
毒舌魔力
to be mean.
谢谢你来帮忙
Thank you so much for helping us out.
反正雷纳要上班
Ah, yeah. Rainer has work, anyways.
他情人节这天
He does this Valentine's day thing
-都会用雷达追踪丘比特  -好有爱
- where he tracks cupid on the radar. - Aww, cute.
莉莉今天能晚点睡觉
Oh, and Lily gets to stay up a little later tonight
因为她在学校做了一件勇敢的事
because she had a big-girl moment at school.
没错  有个男生杰格  这歌名也能当名字了
Yes, this boy Jagger -- 'cause that's a name now --
嘲笑她  她当着大家的面教训了他一顿
teased her and she told him off in front of everybody.
我们为你感到骄傲  因为你用自己的话教育了他
And we're proud of you because you used your words.
她用的是我们的话  我们给她写过一段话
She used our words. We wrote her a little speech.
她狠狠地用来给那孩子上了一课
She really told that kid off good.
我们的社会教导女性要谦逊
Our society encourages women to be unassertive,
所以我们要想尽办法让莉莉更强大
so we need to do everything we can to -- to really empower lily.
我们虽然不追求女人
We may not get women,
但这恰恰让我们更理解女性
but that allows us to really get women.
我们不跟女性搞在一起
We may not hook up with women,
但我们真的很了解女性
but we really understand women.
我刚才就说得够清楚了
I think it was clear when I said that.
所以为什么要"早点开始约会"
So, what's with this whole "going out early" thing.
我们很久没有到外面约会过了
Well, it's been forever since we've had a date-night out,
所以我们列出了六件情人节心愿
and so we made a little list of the six things
是我们一直想做但没机会做的
that we love to do but never get to do.
真可悲
Ugh, pathetic.
我们可以这么吐槽自己  但你不行
Okay, we get to say that, not you.
不不不  是迪兰
No, no, no, it's Dylan.
每年情人节他都发短信给我  求我跟他上床
He texts me every Valentine's day begging to hook up.
的确挺悲哀
Oh, that is sad.
就是啊  几乎每次都失败
I know. It almost never works.
老家伙们
All right, you old bags,
把假牙戴上  带我出去浪
put your teeth in, you're taking me out.
萨尔  你怎么来了
Sal, what are you doing here?
今天是情人节
It's Valentine's day and my
而我的新德国男友维尔纳去外地了
new German boyfriend, Werner, is out of town,
我不喜欢一个人喝闷酒
and I don't like to drink alone.
前半句是真的
The first part's true.
其实我们已经订好计划了
Well, actually, we have plans.
但现在你们有更好的计划了
Aw, but now you have better plans.
福斯塔可以照看萨米
Fausta here can babysit Sammy
和那边那个亚洲娃
and General Tso over there.
萨米  跟你基佬叔叔们问好
Sammy, tell your guncles hello
用我教你的那样
like I taught you.
幸会
Enchante.
我正目睹的是什么情况
Ahh! What am I looking at here?
我要从娃娃抓起把他培养成基
I'm raising him gay.
告诉你米奇尔叔叔你觉得他那条裤子怎么样
Tell Uncle Mitchell what you think about those pants.
丑得惨绝人寰
Tragic.
他记住了
Oh, it's sticking!
快来  我们走
So, come on. Let's go. Uh...
如果有她照看孩子们
Hey, if she's watching the kids,
我不想当多余的第四者
I don't want to be a fourth wheel,
所以让我跟你们仨一起去吧
so I'll just come and join you three.
好主意
That-that sounds great.
米奇尔  我们去壁炉旁聊两句好吗
Mitchell, can I talk to you over by the fireplace?
好
Yeah, yeah.
-我们的计划怎么办  -你了解萨尔
- Hey, so what about our plans? - Look, you know Sal.
如果我们不答应她是不会走的
She's not gonna leave until we agree to this.
我们先哄她俩喝起来
So, look, we'll just get the two of them drinking.
她们不会注意到我们悄悄溜走
They won't even notice when we slip away,
然后我们就回到自己的心愿表上
and, you know, get back to our list.
-真是个好计划  -是吧
- That's a good plan. - Yeah.
反正我本来也不想做心愿表上的第一项
You know what? I didn't even want to do number one anyway.
那让我觉得自己肮脏又羞愧
It makes me feel dirty and ashamed.
好吧  那就不去起司蛋糕餐厅了
Okay, well, bye-bye, Cheesecake Factory.
就这样吧
Wow. All right.
我今天请二位过来是因为
I asked you guys to come in today because
乔送了我非常不合适的情人节礼物
Joe has given me a very, um, inappropriate Valentine's Day gift.
我想这应该是他从家里拿来的吧
I assume that he got this from home?
克拉克老师  我太抱歉了
Ms. Clarke, I am so sorry.
我保证乔根本不明白他在做什么
I'm sure that Joe doesn't even know what he was doing.
看来我终于有机会和儿子抢着看
Looks like I'm finally gonna get to fight with one son
《体育画报泳装女郎特辑》了
over the Sports Illustrated swimsuit issue.
杰  这不好笑
Jay, this is not funny.
我家族里的男人总是太过"敢性"
I come from a very long line of overly sexy men.
我表亲理卡多是性加者
My cousin Ricardo, he had a sex addition.
你是想说性"瘾"吧
You mean "addiction."
是的  抱歉
Uh, yeah, sorry.
他在家里"瘾"盖了一间炮房
He built an addiction onto his house
只用来和众多女友做爱
for making love to his many girlfriends.
你们只要让乔知道
Well, Joe just needs to know
送这种礼物是不合适的就好了
that this type of gift is not okay.
您是对的  我会和他谈谈的
And you're right, and I'm gonna talk to him.
我做错事了吗
Did I do something wrong?
你的确未经同意从妈妈的抽屉里偷拿东西
You did take something out of your mom's drawer without asking.
但这次我就先睁一只眼闭一只眼吧
But I'm gonna give you a pass on that one.
重点是  你送那种礼物非常不合适
The thing is, the gift was inappropriate.
可是你也送妈妈内裤啊
Well, you give underpants to Mom.
没错
True.
你每年都送
You do it every year.
你可以送那种礼物
Look, you can give that kind of thing
给你妻子或女朋友
to your wife or your girlfriend.
但送老师就不能这样了  知道吗
But it's a little bit different when it's your teacher, okay?
好吧  我能回到宁静室去了吗
Fine. Can I go back to the quiet room now?
我已经错过一半的午睡时间了
I already missed half of my nap.
你知道我不午睡会怎么样
You know how I get.
当然  去吧
Sure. Go ahead.
都讲清楚了
Everything's squared away.
克拉克老师  抱歉给您添麻烦了
Ms. Clarke, sorry for the trouble.
请问内衣可以还给我吗
May I have that back?
天啊  不好意思
Oh, my gosh. I'm sorry.
我都不知道人类身材能到如此境界
I didn't know that real humans could have these dimensions.
-谢谢  -过奖了
- Thanks. - Thank you.
我好像不小心掉出了备份的酒店房卡
I seem to have dropped my spare hotel key.
-菲尔  -嘘
- Phil -- - Shh.
无论这个菲尔是谁  不必惊动他
No need to call whoever this Phil is.
你很安全
You're in no danger.
这张房卡是街尾华美达酒店422号房的
This key is to room 422 at the Ramada down the street.
找到机会就溜出来
Slip out when you can.
我会先把烟雾警报器关掉
I'll pre-disable the smoke detectors
这样在你甩掉那条得体阔腿裤时
so you don't set it off when you shimmy out
就不会因为太过惹火触发警报了
of those sensible wide-leg trousers.
在过去几年的情人节里
For the past several Valentine's,
我们会变身性感第二人格
we've adopted sexy alter egos --
狂野又随性的朱莉安娜
Juliana, wild and spontaneous,
和克莱夫  这位对
And Clive, passionate collector
搜集美女和古董航海图十分有热情的男人
of beautiful women and antique sailing maps.
克莱夫  我很喜欢这个主意
Clive, I love this id-
保留点体力  亲爱的
Save that energy, my dear.
在这间酒店房间时间不长
This hotel has a very short memory
但有很长的室外楼梯要爬
and a very long outdoor staircase.
克莱尔  你得把这些合同签好
Claire, you have to finish signing these contracts.
你好  菲尔
Hey, Phil.
我不是菲尔
Phil? No.
我叫克莱夫  朋友
Name's Clive, friend.
或许你能管一会儿事
Say, maybe you could take over here for a bit.
我会把你们女老板完整无缺送回来的
I'll make sure the boss lady's back in one piece
最晚不超过...
no later than --
有没有搞错
Oh, come on.
-你好  菲尔  -他现在是克莱夫
- Hi, Phil. - It's Clive, actually.
他们之间有玩角色扮演  就像你和你姐姐
Apparently they have a thing like how you and your sister
扮成毛绒玩具去参加那些聚会一样
go to those conventions dressed like stuffed animals.
克莱尔  你两点的预约到了
Oh. Uh, Claire, your 2:00 is here
你不能迟到
and you can't be late.
菲尔  我真的很感激你做的这些  真的
Phil, look, I really appreciate this. I do.
-只是我  -我去花店问过了
- It's just that -- - So, I spoke to the florist.
原来我的仰慕者
Turns out my admirer
是从普里契特衣柜公司订的花
sent these from Pritchett's Closets.
或许我的情路不顺  但我不用我妈
I may have a sad love life, but I don't need my mommy
送花来帮我抬高自尊心
trying to boost my self-esteem.
如果你真的想让我更有自信
And if you really want to give me some confidence,
为什么不在桌子上也摆张我的照片
how about a picture of me on your desk,
而不是只摆海莉和卢克的照片
and not just Haley and Luke.
首先  花不是我送你的
First of all, I didn't give you those flowers.
其次  我摆了你的照片
Second of all, there is a picture of you.
哪去了
Where is it?
问候您
Salutations.
你好
Yes, hello.
我有会要开
I've got a meeting.
本  你把合同什么的搞定
Ben, you're gonna finish the contract stuff.
玛格丽特  艾丽克斯交给你
Margaret, you're gonna take Alex.
你们去查是谁用我们的账户订花  好吗
You're gonna find out who's using our account for flowers, okay?
菲尔  亲爱的
Phil, honey,
我们晚点再庆祝情人节  好吗
We'll do Valentine's Day later, okay?
那个穿斗篷的人怎么那么眼熟
Do I know that guy in the cloak?
他是铰链专家  你可能在这见过他
Ah, hinge specialist. You might've seen him around.
遇到新奇的转环和角度奇怪的钩扣
He's the guy for offbeat swivels
我们都找他
and rare-beveled hook joints.
你刚刚说的一切都太挑逗人了
I find everything you just said very titil-
晚餐时我再弥补你  我保证
We'll make up for this later over dinner, I promise.
我一切都计划好了
I've got it all planned.
我都没必要搞克莱夫这一出
This whole Clive thing wasn't even necessary.
克莱尔早就计划好和我一起吃晚餐了
Claire was taking me out to dinner all along.
浪漫还像以往一样浓烈
Romance strong as ever.
玛格丽特  快帮我和菲尔
Margaret, get a reservation
预定一下晚餐  哪都行
for me and Phil tonight, anywhere.
我忙得根本没有闲心想这些事了
I've got too much going on to even think about it.
维尔纳人可好了
Werner is great.
他是个有钱的音乐家
You know, he's a rich musician,
总去巡演  不缠人
tours a lot, no strings.
那个吧
Well, um...
今天玩得真开心  但我们该...
...This has been fun, but we should, uh...
你哪也别想去  红毛
You're not going anywhere, carrot bottom.
我的天  那是雷纳吗
Oh, my god. Is that Rainer?
他为什么和别的女人在一起
Why is he with another woman?
貌似有捉奸好戏看了
That sounds cheat-y.
他是海莉的天气预报员男友
That's Haley's weatherman boyfriend.
-抱歉  小海  -我们快走吧
- Sorry, Hale. - We need to leave.
不行  你得和他当面对质
No, you got to go confront him.
我很难受  喝了好几杯了  不去比较好
Mm. I'm upset. I've had a couple drinks. No.
好吧
Okay.
和其他加拿大杂技演员一起世界巡演有趣吗
So, what's it like touring the world with other Canadian acrobats?
什么
What?
我们还以为你是杂技团的呢
We just assumed you were a member of cirque du soleil.
是啊  因为你柔软到能把
Yup, because you're bending over backwards
脑袋弯到背后来逃避面对事实
to avoid standing up for yourself.
为其他女性
And setting a good example
树立好榜样
for other women.
你们都这么想的吗
You both were thinking that?
-好  -终于
- Fine. - Finally.
我差点以为她
I was beginning to think she was weaker
比米奇尔的下巴还脆弱
than Mitchell's jawline.
大家都知道你为什么留那玩意儿
Everyone knows why you grew that thing.
好吧  这吐槽居然是来自一个
Okay, this coming from the woman who -- who won't admit
不愿意承认自己在情人节
that she's upset that her boyfriend abandoned her
被男友抛下的事实而不开心的人
on Valentine's day.
你不是刚跟印第安人
Oh, and didn't you just get back from learning
学种玉米回来吗
how to plant corn with the Indians?
因为在我们来看你就像早期定居者
Because you look, to us, like an early settler.
定居者
Settler.
我们是说你找了配不上你的人[定居]
We're saying that you settle.
你们在家排练过了  对吧
You practice this at home, don't you?
-才没有  -才没有
- We do not. - We do not.
我知道那雷声不可能是天使在打保龄球...
Now, I knew it couldn't be angels bowling, so --
我以为你今天要上班
I thought you were working today.
我们不是说好你再也不穿这件毛衣的吗
And didn't we agree that you never wear that sweater again?
-我...  -不好意思
- My...  - Excuse me.
我们在约会
We're kind of on a date right now.
-海莉  -省省吧  你这满嘴谎言
- Uh, Haley. - Oh, save it, you lying,
脚踏两条船的中年"指"男癌
cheating, middle-aged pointer.
你这人就是这样  指来指去的
That's what you do, you know -- you point.
靠一指神功挣钱  我们结束了
You point for your money! We are done!
情人节快乐
Happy Valentine's day.
我的发型
My hair.
刚才感觉真是又疯狂
Oh, that was crazy
又酸爽又糟糕  我现在不知道要怎么办
and great and awful and I don't know what to do.
我要回家了
I'm just gonna go home.
什么  别啊  我现在喜欢你了
What?! No! I like you now.
维尔纳有一艘带酒吧的游艇  一起去吧
Werner has a yacht with a full bar. Let's go.
这么嗨  我才不会让你回家
I'm not letting you go home in this mood.
好吧  去船上酒吧喝酒感觉像是
Okay, well, you know, that sounds kind of like
女生的活动  那...
a girl thing, so...
如果是雷纳打来找借口的
Oh, okay, if that's Rainer calling to make excuses,
别接
don't answer.
是可怜的迪兰打来求约炮的
It's just pathetic Dylan trying to hook up again.
我来搞定  嘿  小可爱
Let me handle this. Hey, boo boo.
又一位女性受我们激励
Well, another woman empowered.
-这就是我们的使命  -没错
- It's what we do. - Yes, it is.
好了  回到心愿表
Okay, back to the list.
等等  是莉莉
Oh, wait one second. It's Lily.
亲爱的  有什么事吗
Hey, honey. Is everything okay?
杰格听了我们那套话语很受伤
Jagger was very hurt by our speech.
莉莉没回他短信
She didn't answer his texts
因为我们叫她别回
'cause we told her not to.
很好
Good.
-他离家出走了  -真的吗
- He ran away. - He did?
大家正组成人链
People are forming a human chain
在森林里找他
to search for him in the woods.
好的  亲爱的  我们马上回家  好吗
Okay, honey, well, we'll be home soon, all right?
你觉得杰格这件事
Do you think we have some responsibility
咱们有责任吗
in this Jagger situation?
没有  没有
Ah...No. No.
他们自己要住到森林附近的
They -- they chose to build near the woods.
我们的建议是好的
Good advice is good advice, okay?
-也对  -二位  海莉呢
- That's right. - You guys, where's Haley?
她在码头边的一艘船上
Um, she is on a boat in the marina,
把你抛到脑后[后视镜外]了
putting you in her rearview mirror.
-船有后视镜吧  -应该有
- Boats have those, don't they? - I think so.
二位  我只是让那女士以为
You guys, I was only letting that woman
我们在约会
think we were on a date
因为她是一个名人网站的站长
because she runs a celebrity site
专从狗仔手里买照片
that buys photos from paparazzi, okay?
我想把其中一张拿回来
I was trying to get one of me back
因为照片里有海莉  就是这张
because Haley is in it and this is the photo.
-不  天  不  -我的天
- No. God, no. - Oh, my gosh.
刚起床的发型  喷嚏脸  UGG丑拖鞋
Bedhead, sneeze face, and ugg slippers?
海莉不接我电话
And now Haley's not answering my calls
而15分钟后我还得笑着
and somehow I'm supposed to smile through a weather report
播报天气
in 15 minutes?
别慌  雷纳
Pull yourself together, Rainer.
你可是天气播报员
You're a weatherman.
你会不会觉得我们的建议...
Do you think our advice --
糟糕透顶  对  对
Sucked? Yes. Yes.
我们得在海莉勾搭上迪兰前
We need to get to that boat
赶到船上去
before Haley hooks up with dylan.
她不会做那么蠢的事吧
She wouldn't do something that stupid.
你看到那双Ugg丑鞋了吧
Did you see the uggs?
好吧  对  对  对
Okay. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
妈  我回来了
Mom, I'm home.
我们买了情人节礼物
We got Valentines.
你好  丘利夫人
Oh, hi, Mrs. Kewley.
派对结束了吗
Is the party over?
出了点小状况
We had an incident.
你儿子给我们贝莉
Your son gave my Bailey
送了一个很奇怪的情人节礼物
a very strange Valentine's gift.
真对不起
I am so sorry.
你爸不是已经跟你说过这件事了吗
Didn't your father talk to you about this already?
对啊  他说可以送给女朋友
Yeah, and he said it's okay to give it to a girlfriend.
我们走了  贝莉才不是他女朋友
We're going. And Bailey is certainly not his girlfriend.
那是她的福气
She would be lucky!
那是贝莉吗
Is that Bailey?
我记得乔对她有意思
'Bause I think Joe has a little thing for her.
他的确有很有"意思"的东西给她
Yeah, he did have a little thing for her.
在这儿  他又来了
It's here. He did it again.
我就知道不能放心交给你去教育他
I knew I shouldn't have trusted you talking to him,
就算他杀了人你也会帮他脱罪
because you will let him get away with murder
因为他就是迷你版的你  你还特高兴
because he's a mini you and you like it.
更糟的是什么你知道吗
And you know what's worse?
你对曼尼那么小心眼
That you're so mean to Manny
就是因为他跟你不一样
because he's different than you.
首先  乔不是迷你版的我
First off, Joe is not a mini me.
垃圾  辣鸡  蜡鸡
Crap. Crapola. Crapinski.
好吧  可能有一点
Well, maybe a little,
也许我却是有点喜欢这事
and maybe I kind of like it.
可你为什么要把乔身上我的影子去掉呢
But why would you want to knock the Jay out of Joe?
你从拥有一个宝贝变成两个宝贝呢
Instead of one trophy, you get two.
到了  谢天谢地
Okay, thank God.
她在这呢
Oh, gosh, there she is.
你们怎么来了
What are you guys doing here?
需要水手来完成你们
Need a sailor to cross off number four
情人节心愿表的第四条吗
on that Valentine's day list of yours?
跟萨尔待了一会儿  嘴都没把门了
Was that mean i've been around Sal, I've lost my filter.
你知道吗  人非圣贤孰能无过
You know what? We all make mistakes.
等我们告诉你一个
Which is a-a funny thing to remember
很可笑的误会后  你回想起来都会觉得好笑
when we tell you about a very funny misunderstanding.
卡梅隆  米奇尔  真是惊喜
Cameron, Mitchell, what a pleasant surprise.
萨尔  你还好吗  你看起来怪怪的
Sal, you okay? You seem not yourself.
是啊  咋不眨眼呢
Yeah, I feel like you used to blink.
我听了你们的建议  给维尔纳打了电话
I took your advice. Called Werner.
跟他说我不想就这么委身下嫁
Told him I wasn't going to settle.
然后...
How did that --
然后呢
How -- how did that go?
他本来觉得我们或许能有未来
He was thinking that we might be something special,
然后我给他下了最后通牒
and then I gave him the ultimatum,
结果他说  "也许我们有缘无分"
and he said, "Maybe we're not actually meant to be."
什么情况  萨尔  你在干什么
I don't know what's happening. S-sal, w-what are you doing?
收拾收拾
Straightening up.
这是所有东西的...
You know, a place for everything...
-别  -...好去处
- No. - ...everything in its place.
这个如何
Hey, what about this?
这其实是从二战知名战舰上淘来的宝贝
This was actually salvaged from the Bismarck.
好...
That's...
你还助纣为虐
Why are you helping?
爽  男人都是坏东西
Feels good. Men suck.
不不  不是所有男人
No, no, n-not all men, okay?
我们刚跟雷纳谈了
We -- we just talked to Rainer,
他不是在约会
and, um, that wasn't a date.
什么
What?!
为什么砸了
Okay, why did you break that?
因为现在我气的是你们
'Cause now I'm mad at you!
你们让我跟他分手
You made me break up with him!
我的天 我得给雷纳打个电话
Oh, my God. Now I have to call Rainer,
还有迪兰
and Dylan.
-萨尔  亲爱的  -萨尔  别...
- Oh, Sal, sweetie... - Sal, you gotta --
酒洒了
You're spilling there.
-提起来  瓶口提起来  -笨手笨脚
- Lift it, lift it. - Oh, clumsy, clumsy.
让一切化作灰烬随风而去吧
I'll just make it all go away.
-别  我们还在船上呢  -住手  萨尔
- No! We are still on board. - No, Sal.
抱歉我们叫你打给维尔纳
We are sorry we made you call Werner.
我们不知道事情会变成这样
We didn't know that that was gonna happen.
你得理解一下你...
So you have to understand that you...
米奇尔你不来帮忙吗
Mitchell you want to step in here?
我吹到都头晕了
I'm getting dizzy.
我...
I am --
-别拦我  -不许再这样了
- Stop it! - Okay, no more.
不许再点火柴了  不许了
No more matches. No more matches.
好了  可是我也不知道该怎么做
Okay, what -- I don't know what to do.
好吧  或许我们可以...
Okay, well, maybe we should just...
维纳尔宝贝的托尼奖奖杯
Werner's precious Tony award.
他把它留在船上做为终极催情神器
He keeps in at sea as the ultimate aphrodisiac.
这不对女人催情吧
For women?
托尼奖是美国剧场界最高荣誉
参选项目包含话剧与音乐剧  受到同性恋关注
再会[德语]  托尼奖最佳编曲奖杯
Auf Wiedersehen, award for best orchestration.
-要命了  -不行  萨尔  萨尔
- Oh, my God. - No. Sal, Sal.
-海利  快来帮忙  -不行
- Haley, help. - No.
我可不要告诉你同志儿子
I will not tell your gay son
你把一座托尼奖奖杯丢进海里乐
that you threw a Tony into the ocean.
-你快给我  -不要
- Give it to me! - No!
天啊  她掉下去了吗
Oh, my god. Did she fall in?
没有
No.
"她"安全在我手里呢
I've got her right here.
萨尔  我们真的很抱歉
Sal, we are so sorry.
如果不是我们出的馊主意
If it wasn't for our stupid advice,
你就不会没事找事  事情也就不会变这样
you would've left things alone and things might've been okay.
-你闭嘴  -好  好的
- Shut up! - Okay, okay.
冷冷的海水打醒我  让我看清了现实
That cold water woke me up to the hard truth --
老娘聪明绝顶  闭月羞花
I'm smart, I'm beautiful,
床技过人  却放弃寻找更好的人就嫁人了
I'm legendary in bed, yet I do settle.
维纳尔的确是配不上我啊
I mean, Werner is not good enough for me.
我能懂为啥你们俩白痴为啥不再找了
I mean, I get why you two idiots settled.
毕竟对方就是你们能找到最好的人了
This is the best you're gonna do, right here.
你们俩简直王八配绿豆
You're perfectly matched.
这么看的话  某种程度上感觉好甜啊
Well, it's kind of sweet when you look at it that way.
是啊  与你相遇好幸运
Yeah. We are very lucky.
情人节快乐
Happy Valentine's day.
是啊  情人节快乐
Yeah, happy Valentine's day.
闭嘴  懂得察言观色好吗  基佬们
Shut up. Read a room, poofs.
玛格丽特说是你负责保管电话记录
Hey. Margaret said you keep the phone records.
怎么了  你为什么需要拿记录
Why? What do you need them for?
我想找出是谁送我的花
I'm still trying to find out who sent me those flowers.
-你收在这里面吗  -别打开
- You keep them in here? - No, don't.
别啊
Don't.
本  为什么我的这张照片在你的抽屉里
Ben, why do you have this photo of me in your desk drawer?
我猜可能是有人在整我吧
I think someone's pranking me, probably.
-我要走了  -好的
- I'm gonna go. - Okay.
别走  其实花是我送的  好了吧
Wait, look. I sent the flowers, okay?
当你去年夏天来这里打工时
When you temped here last summer,
我也被你的魅力所打动
I became tempted by your charms.
谢谢欣赏  但你不是都要40岁了吗
Well, thank you, but aren't you like 40?
什么  我才26岁啊
What? I'm 26.
我  我小时候吃糖上瘾
I -- I had a sweetart addiction when I was a kid
永久伤害到胶原蛋白  所以显老
and I permanently damaged my collagen.
我谈过一个又一个
Wow. I've been in a series of bizarre,
离奇又羞耻的恋爱
shame-filled relationships.
你是我妈的员工  而我还在家里蹲
You work for my mother. You still live at home.
-再看看你吃的各种药  快吻我  -什么鬼
- Look at all those medications. Kiss me. - What?
你刚才的举动很屌
Whoa. Okay, that was very cool,
可是我得告诉你  我把人生奉献给衣柜
but you should know that I have dedicated my life to closets,
我疯狂迷恋你外公
I am obsessed with your grandfather,
而且睡觉都抱着穿着女睡衣的等身枕头睡
and I sleep with a body pillow that I put a nightgown on.
别再说了  你越说越吸引我
Stop, you're making it better.
给  今晚客人很多啊  先生
Here you go. Busy night, sir.
想必您已经订了位子
I assume you have a reservation?
是的  我妻子订的
Yes. My wife made it.
虽然送我礼物这件事她办砸了
She kind of dropped the ball on my gift,
但她成功在大名鼎鼎的恩里克餐厅订到位
but she came through with a table at the legendary Enrico's.
先生  很抱歉  恩里克是前面另一家餐厅
I'm sorry, sir. Enrico's is a couple doors down.
就你一个人吗
So, just yourself?
不是  我今晚会跟老婆在这见面
Uh, no, I'll be meeting my wife tonight.
你这么乐观就对了
That's the spirit.
我错过了什么
What'd I miss?
这个薪水太高技术太水的傻子推杆没进
This overpaid bum missed a putt.
我怎么能不喜闻乐见
I'm supposed to not like this.
杰  骂我智障吧
Well, call me an idiot, Jay.
的确  我跟亚历克莎一起进浴缸泡澡了
Sure enough, Alexa and I did end up in a hot tub together.
但在她喝到第三瓶啤酒时
But around her third beer,
我建议她喝点水免得脱水
I suggested she have some water to stay hydrated.
她就想用嘴堵上我的嘴
She tried to shut me up by kissing me,
我的确挺享受  可她一直叫我崔维斯
which I liked, but she kept calling me Travis.
要命了  他还在唧唧歪歪吗
Oh, my God! Is it still talking?!
乔  不许你这么不尊敬你哥哥
Joe, you don't ever disrespect your brother like that.
也再也不许你送其他小女孩或任何人内裤
And no more giving underwear to little girls, or anyone else,
因为这很痴汉还很欧洲人
'cause it's creepy and European.
罚你回房间待着
Now go to your room.
你的孩子遗传到你最佳的优点的确很开心
It's fun when your kids get your best qualities,
但当你看到他们也学到了
but it's a kick in the gut when they pick up stuff
你身上的缺点时  也很难受
you hate about yourself.
我看到了我丑陋没耐心的一面
I saw that ugly, impatient part of me
从我可爱的儿子嘴里冒出来
coming out of my adorable son.
但公平来说  他可爱的部分也遗传自我
In fairness, that adorable part also came from me.
我们都遗传到了我妈的红粉面颊  松软双唇
We both got my mom's crab-apple cheeks and pillow lips.
亲爱的  抱歉我迟到了
Hi, honey. I'm sorry I'm late.
我们出了场大事故
We had a whole incident -- mwah --
仓库里有台涂料混合器炸了
at the warehouse, a paint mixer blew up.
幸好我办公室里还留了这么一套吊带裤
Luckily I had these overalls in my office I could...
你生气了  是吧
Oh, you're mad, aren't you?
生气咩
Mad?
毕竟  这是我们度过最棒的情人节吗
I mean, was this the best Valentine's day we've ever had?
不是
No.
那这是最烂的吗  是的
Was it the worst? Yes.
我给了你很棒的礼物
I gave you a great gift.
我还试着到你办公室给你惊喜
I tried to surprise you at the office.
而你报答我的方式就是订位吃
You repaid the effort by making a reservation
卡车司机餐厅  还穿成像《汤姆历险记》男主
at a truck stop and dressing up like Tom Sawyer.
或许这种事在任何人身上都可能发生  克莱尔
But hey, maybe this happens to everyone, Claire.
浪漫如浪花  浪花死沙滩
Romance fizzles. Magic dies.
但至少我们可以记录下浪漫死去的确切时间呢
At least we can mark the exact time it happened to us,
多亏了你送我这手表
thanks to my new watch,
一只只有1950年的超忙电话接线员
which only a switchboard operator from the 1950s
能保持它持续上了发条
could keep wound.
你是说这只表吗
You mean this watch?
胡迪尼手铐
The houdini handcuffs.
我去上了魔术课来给你当情人节惊喜
I've been taking magic lessons as a Valentine's surprise.
等等  那个出现在你办公室的铰链销售员
Wait a minute. The supposed hinge salesman at your office.
伟大的大魔师
The great majesto.
我就说嘛  我没认出他
Of course. I didn't recognize him
因为他没穿他招牌的问号拖地长袍
without his floor-length robe covered in question marks.
而且我们真的在过旁边的那家
And we also really do have a reservation
超棒餐厅有订位
at that really nice place down the street.
所以我们赶紧买单走人吧
So, we should probably get your check.
不好意思  买单
Excuse me. Can we get the check?
但是你穿这样能去...
But are you really dressed for...
太赞了  我...
So wonderful. I can't...
走吧  亲爱的  我们该走了
Come on, honey. We should get going.
等等  你有手铐钥匙吗
Wait, uh, do you have the key?
没有  但是你有
No. But you do.
我不配有你如此贤妻
I don't deserve you.
亲爱的  你给了我一个永生难忘的情日
Honey, you gave me a V.D. I will carry with me always.
就好好说"情人节"吧
Let's say "Valentine's day."
我一直觉得你赢不了我的礼物  但你真赢了
You know, I never thought you'd beat my gift, but you did.
亲爱的
Oh, honey.
我开始觉得我的秋千礼物像是挥棒落空
I'm beginning to think that mine was a swing and a miss.
才没有  你的礼物正中红心
Hardly. Yours was fantastic.
要我说  秋千老婆两不空
But how about a swing with a Miss?
-你今天真是绝了  -对啊
- You are killing it today! - I know!
你又把它罩上了吗
Did you cover that again?
没有啊  太奇怪了
I didn't. That's weird.
什么鬼
What the hell?
我把它移到了门廊
I transported it to the porch.
不用谢
You're welcome.
我没请他这么做啊
I didn't ask him to do that...
也没告诉过他我们住哪里
or tell him where we live.